<?xml version="1.0" encoding="US-ASCII"?>
    <mobs>
      <mob name="ElderRose">
        <dialogue id="awakenings">
          <text>You have stirred. Good. You were half dead when we found you. Rest now. You are safe.</text>
          <options>
            <option target="shir">Where am I?</option>
            <option target="rose">Who are you?</option>
            <option target="rescue">What happened?</option>
          </options>
        </dialogue>
        <dialogue id="shir">
          <text>You are in the Shir Valley, in the home of Elder Rose.</text>
        </dialogue>
        <dialogue id="rose">
          <text>Why, I am Elder Rose, of course. This is the village of Finn's Glen</text>
        </dialogue>
        <dialogue id="rescue">
          <text>
          "A group of farmers found you collapsed in the wilderness. You were holding this..."
          She points out a blade among your belongings. 
          "I had you brought here and have nursed you back to health."
          </text>
          <options>
            <option target="sword">What of the sword?</option>
            <option target="tomb">What was I doing out there?</option>
            <option target="end">I wish to leave, now. [END CONVERSATION]</option>
          </options>
        </dialogue>
        <dialogue id="sword">
          <text> 
          The Elder looks apprehensive. "I dare not touch it. It bears the mark of the Uncrowned King."
          She studies the sword for a moment and looks at you worriedly. 
          "Any who bore this blade are doomed to whatever foul magic enchants it."
          </text>
        </dialogue>
        <dialogue id="tomb">
          <text>
          "There is a tomb to the last Good King of Klathia just west of the Glen. Perhaps you were plundering it?"
          </text>
        </dialogue>
        <dialogue id="end">
          <text>
          You are free to leave, but know this: The Shir Valley is relatively safe, 
          but the Uncrowned King holds court upon the Klathian throne. His armies 
          are vast, and his sorceries vile. The elven queen hides in her forest 
          realm and the dwarven king cowers in his mountain hall. Any who would openly defy
          him, especially those he has cursed, would be doomed to fail. Even those
          whose claim to the throne is strong.
          </text>
      </mob>
      <mob name = "Uncrowned King">
        <dialogue>
        </dialogue>
      </mob>
    </mobs>